<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>

<pdHelp xmlns="http://www.ibm.com/visualutils/pdhelpcontent"
	xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
	xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.ibm.com/visualutils/pdhelpcontent http://www.ibm.com/visualutils/pdhelpcontent">

	<pluginCategory id="com.ibm.hcls.sdg.ui">
 		<pageHelp id="DataAnalysisNewWizardPage">
	    	<title>Create a Data Analysis Project</title>
	    	<shortDescription>Use a Data Analysis Project to analyze data that is contained in XML files. </shortDescription>
            <moreDescription>
              <p>Creating a project is the first step in analyzing your data. After you create the project, you analyze sample data files, and then create a target model. The second step is to generate Data Analysis tools that map your input data to your target model.</p>
            </moreDescription>
            <topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bd24240_.htm">
				<label>Data analysis concepts</label>
			</topic>
	    </pageHelp>
		<fieldHelp id="DA_Profile">
			<title>Data Analysis Profile</title>
			<description>
				<p>User-defined profiles facilitate the analysis and viewing of your data. An IBM-provided profile additionally highlights revealed parts of your data.</p>
			</description>
		</fieldHelp>
		<fieldHelp id="DA_Schema">
			<title>Data Analysis Schema</title>
			<description><p>If you chose a user-defined profile, select the schema that governs the structure of your data. The schema is either a single file with the .xsd extension, or a .zip file if the schema consists of several XSD files.</p>
			</description>
			</fieldHelp>
		<fieldHelp id="DA_Namespace">
			<title>Data Analysis Namespace</title>
			<description><p>The namespace is inherited from the selected schema.</p>
			</description>
		</fieldHelp>
		
		
		<pageHelp id="DA_LoadDocuments">
	    	<title>Load documents</title>
	    	<shortDescription>Specify the directory that contains the sample XML data files that you want to analyze. Optionally, pick a subset of files in that directory. </shortDescription>
	    </pageHelp>
		
		<fieldHelp id="DA_SourceDirectory">
			<title>Source directory</title>
			<description>
				<p>A directory in your file system that contains the XML sample documents for building a Data Analysis Model. Only new data and data structures are added to the Data Analysis Model. If your sample document does not add any new structure or data to the Data Analysis Model, the sample document is not stored.</p>
			</description>
		</fieldHelp>
		
		<fieldHelp id="DA_FilePattern">
			<title>File Pattern</title>
			<description><p>To select a subset of files from the source directory, enter a wildcard expression using '*' for multiple characters and '?' for a single character. For example, to match all files that start with the string 'myproj', and have the extension '.xml', type: <br /></p>
				<p>myproj*.xml<br /></p>
			</description>
		</fieldHelp>
		
		<pageHelp id="DA_LoadDocuments">
	    	<title>Load documents</title>
	    	<shortDescription>Specify the directory that contains the sample XML data files that you want to analyze. Optionally, pick a subset of files in that directory. </shortDescription>
	    </pageHelp>
		
		<pageHelp id="DA_DAPEditorOverview">
	    	<title>Data Analysis Project Overview</title>
	    	<shortDescription>This editor gives an overview of the available resources in the project and the tasks that you can complete.</shortDescription>
	    </pageHelp>
		
		
		<pageHelp id="DA_LoadSummary">
	    	<title>Summary of analyzed documents</title>
	    	<shortDescription>This is a summary of your analyzed documents. </shortDescription>
	    	<moreDescription><p>Click Highlight New Elements to highlight additions to the Data Analysis Model. This function is available only if new elements are added to the Data Analysis Model. A file that does not conform to the schema, or that adds nothing to the Data Analysis Model, is not kept as a sample document.
	    	  </p></moreDescription>
	    </pageHelp>
		
		<pageHelp id="DA_DataAnalysisModelOff">
	    	<title>Off Button</title>
	    	<shortDescription>Turn off all highlighting and filters within the Data Analysis Model.</shortDescription>
	    </pageHelp>

		<pageHelp id="DA_DataAnalysisTargetModelRoot">
	    	<title>Root Object Name</title>
	    	<shortDescription>Specify the root of your target model which is used as the root of all your output XML messages.</shortDescription>
	    </pageHelp>
		<pageHelp id="DA_DataAnalysisTargetModelNamespace">
	    	<title>Target XML Namespace</title>
	    	<shortDescription>The suggested value for Target XML Namespace is derived from the namespace that the schema that you specified when you created the Data Analysis project uses. To avoid conflicts, the Target XML Namespace must be unique among all target models that are based upon the same schema.</shortDescription>
	    </pageHelp>
	    
		<pageHelp id="DA_DataPaths">
	    	<title>Data Paths</title>
	    	<shortDescription>The element node that you want to move has multiple possible data paths. </shortDescription>
	    <moreDescription>
              <p>Related paths are descendants of the node in the target model that you are adding the element node to. </p>
              <p>Other paths are data paths from other nodes in the target model.</p>
            </moreDescription></pageHelp>

		
		<pageHelp id="GenerateSubflowPage1ValidationBox">
			<title>Validation of input messages</title>
			<shortDescription>Checking this box generates a validation stylesheet. This stylesheet measures input documents against your target model. If elements are found in a document that are not part of the target model, the document fails validation.</shortDescription>
		</pageHelp>
		
		<pageHelp id="GenerateSubflowPage3DBType">
			<title>Database Type</title>
			<shortDescription>To edit the Database Type, left click the root element in the target model editor, then edit the Database Product field in the Relational tab of the Properties view.</shortDescription>
		</pageHelp>
		
		<pageHelp id="GenerateSubflowPage3DBVersion">
			<title>Database Version</title>
			<shortDescription>To edit the Database Version, left click the root element in the target model editor, then edit the Database Version field in the Relational tab of the Properties view.</shortDescription>
		</pageHelp>
		
		<pageHelp id="GenerateSubflowPage3DBName">
	    	<title>Database Name</title>
	    	<shortDescription>The database name, which must match your runtime database definition on your broker.</shortDescription>
	    <moreDescription>
              <p>Your deployed map accesses your database in the runtime. The Database Name is the name of the JDBC provider for your database, as configured on your broker.</p>
              <p></p>
            </moreDescription></pageHelp>
            
         <pageHelp id="TargetModelRelationalPropertiesTableName">
         	<title>Name</title>
         	<shortDescription>To edit this field, edit the corresponding cell in the target model editor.</shortDescription>
         </pageHelp>

		<pageHelp id="TerminologyFlatFileCodePage_FileFormat">
	    	<title>Delimited Format Specification</title>
	    	<shortDescription>Description of the required glossary file format specification.</shortDescription>
	    <moreDescription>
              <p>Delimited glossary files are plain text files, with fields delimited by consistent string characters.
              To automate the extraction process, specify how the file contents are delimited.</p>
              <p></p>
            </moreDescription></pageHelp>
            
		<pageHelp id="TerminologyFlatFileCodePage_Explicit">
	    	<title>Glossary Reference Defined in File</title>
	    	<shortDescription>Plain text files that explicitly state glossary references. Identify the glossary reference in addition to key-value pairs in a delimited plain text format.</shortDescription>
	    <moreDescription>
              <p>Use this option if the glossary file explicitly specifies the glossary reference in addition to key-value pairs in a delimited plain text format. </p>
              <p></p>
            </moreDescription></pageHelp>
		
		<pageHelp id="TerminologyFlatFileCodePage_Implicit">
	    	<title>User-Defined Glossary Reference</title>
	    	<shortDescription>Plain text files that define key-value pairs in a delimited format and require a user-specified glossary reference.</shortDescription>
	    <moreDescription>
              <p>Use this option if the glossary file only specifies the key-value pairings in a delimited plain text format.</p>
              <p></p>
            </moreDescription></pageHelp>
		
	</pluginCategory>
</pdHelp>