<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>
    <context id="DataLineageDocumentsWizard">
      <description>

Create CSV files for Extension Mapping Documents for Compute node data lineage, and CSV files for Extended Data Source Documents for referenced schemas.

<b>Source project</b>
Select the application, library, or project from which to export Data Lineage documents.

<b>File that maps namespace URIs to prefixes</b>
Provide a file that maps namespace URIs to prefixes. The file is a comma-separated values file, with two columns in each row. The first column is namespace URI, and second column is the namespace prefix, for example: 
http://www.ibm.com/wbimb/webservice/sample/OrderService,orderNS
http://www.ibm.com/wbimb/webservice/sample/ShippingService,shipNS

Both namespace URI and namespace prefix must be unique.

To generate a namespace mapping file, type a filename in the field and click Generate.  The generated file is based on the namespace URI defined in the message set and preferred prefix is defined in the case of MRM with XML format. If multiple prefices are used in multiple mxsd files for the same namespace, the very first prefix would be used for the generated namespace mapping file. If a preferred prefix is not found, namespace prefixes starting from genNS0, genNS1, and so forth are used. So, a generated namespace mapping file might look something like this:

http://www.ibm.com/wbimb/webservice/sample/OrderService, genNS0
http://www.ibm.com/wbimb/webservice/sample/ShippingService,genNS1

<b>Extension Mapping Documents that contain rows of mappings between message elements</b>
Select this field to create a report of the transform mapping in Compute nodes of each message flow. Select this field if you intend to create reports in IBM® InfoSphere® Metadata Workbench. 

Typically, you select the "Create inline mappings from subflows in the main message flow" option. Create separate mapping documents for subflows if you are interested only in the transformations in a subflow.  

You can generate mapping documents for a single flow, rather than all flows.

<b>Extended Data Sources that describe the structure of messages</b>
Select this field to create a report of schema definitions. You need information about schemas if you intend to create reports in IBM InfoSphere Metadata Workbench. 


<b>Folder Selection</b><!-- This section is copied to the DataLineageFolderSelection context -->
Select a folder or create a new folder. The wizard creates up to three subfolders in the specified directory: 

- Data Source CSV Files. If "Extended Data Sources that describe the structure of messages" option is selected, all the data source .csv files are created in the "Data Source CSV Files" folder. 
 
- Mapping CSV Files. If "Extension Mapping Documents that contain rows of mappings between message elements" option is selected, all the mapping .csv files are created in the "Mapping CSV Files" folder. 

- Mapping Rejected Files. All the .reject files listing unsupported mappings are created in the "Mapping Rejected Files" folder.
      
      </description>
      <topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bd34061_.htm"  label="Data lineage CSV files"/>
      <topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bd34062_.htm"  label="Data lineage restrictions"/>
<!-- End of copy -->
    </context>
    
    <context id="DataLineageFolderSelection">
      <description>
<b>Folder Selection</b>
Select a folder or create a new folder. The wizard creates up to three subfolders in the specified directory: 

- Data Source CSV Files. If "Extended Data Sources that describe the structure of messages" option is selected, all the data source .csv files are created in the "Data Source CSV Files" folder. 
 
- Mapping CSV Files. If "Extension Mapping Documents that contain rows of mappings between message elements" option is selected, all the mapping .csv files are created in the "Mapping CSV Files" folder. 

- Mapping Rejected Files. All the .reject files listing unsupported mappings are created in the "Mapping Rejected Files" folder.

	  </description>
      <topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bd34061_.htm"  label="Data lineage CSV files"/>
      <topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bd34062_.htm"  label="Data lineage restrictions"/>
    </context>
    <context id="SelectMessageFlow">
    <description>
<b>Message Flow Selection</b>
Select a message flow.

If you selected option "Create separate mapping document for subflows", all main message flow and subflows with file extension .msgflow and .subflow are displayed.

If you selected option "Inline mappings from subflows in the main message flow", only main message flows are displayed.
	</description>
    </context>
</contexts>
