<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>
	<context id="caw">
	    <description><b>Command Assistant wizard</b>
Use this wizard to create, modify or delete runtime components, such as brokers, in the IBM Integration Toolkit.</description>
        <topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bz90400_.htm" label="Configuring brokers for a development environment"/>
	</context>
	
	<context id="dcw">
	    <description><b>Default Configuration wizard - Create</b>
Use this wizard to create the IBM Integration Default Configuration.
When you have created the Default Configuration, you can deploy and run the IBM Integration sample applications.</description>
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/be68210_.htm" label="Creating the Default Configuration"/>
        <topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/be68220_.htm" label="What the Default Configuration wizard does"/>
	</context>
	
	<context id="rdcw">
	    <description><b>Default Configuration wizard - Remove</b>
Use this wizard to remove the IBM Integration Default Configuration.
When you have deleted the Default Configuration, you can no longer deploy and run the IBM Integration sample applications. Use the wizard if you want to recreate the Default Configuration.</description>
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/be68210_.htm" label="Creating the Default Configuration"/>
	</context>
	
	<context id="spwSampleList">
	    <description><b>Prepare the Samples wizard</b>
Use this wizard to prepare or remove a IBM Integration sample.
If you have created the Default Configuration, you can also deploy a sample so that you can run it.
If you have not created the Default Configuration, you can still import a sample into the IBM Integration Toolkit so that you can explore the samples resources without actually running the sample.
Run this wizard for each sample that you want to import or remove.</description>
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/ax20230_.htm" label="Samples"/>
	</context>
	
	<context id="spwSampleAction">
	    <description><b>Prepare the Samples wizard - task</b>
Select a task to perform on the sample.
</description>
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/ax20230_.htm" label="Samples"/>
	</context>
	
</contexts>