<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?NLS TYPE="org.eclipse.help.contexts"?>
<contexts>
  
	<context id="editor">
		<description><b>REST API Editor</b>
This is where you work with a REST API.  
The editor consists of the following sections: Header, Resources, Model Definitions, Error Handling, and Security.
		</description>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12016_.htm" label="Developing integration solutions by using REST APIs"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12040_.htm" label="Defining resources, models, and operations in a REST API"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12017_.htm" label="REST APIs"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12020_.htm" label="Restrictions on Swagger documents"/>
    </context>
            
	<context id="createResource">
		<description><b>Create a Resource with Operations</b>
Create a resource under the existing resource structure with selected default operations. 
Existing resource paths in the API are shown in a tree structure.
A new resource path can be created under the existing path structure by selecting a path container and specifying the path under the container.
Use curly braces ({}) to mark a section of a URL path as replaceable using a path parameter.
Select default operations to be added in the resource to be created.
		</description>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12016_.htm" label="Developing integration solutions by using REST APIs"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12040_.htm" label="Defining resources, models, and operations in a REST API"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12017_.htm" label="REST APIs"/>
    </context>
            
	<context id="modifyResourcePaths">
		<description><b>Modify Resource Paths</b>
Use this dialog to modify one or more resource paths.
Existing resource paths in the API are shown in a tree structure.
A path segment can be modified or removed, and all of the resources with a path containing the segment are affected.
New path segments can be inserted to existing paths.
Use curly braces ({}) to mark a section of a URL path as replaceable using a path parameter.
		</description>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12016_.htm" label="Developing integration solutions by using REST APIs"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12040_.htm" label="Defining resources, models, and operations in a REST API"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12017_.htm" label="REST APIs"/>
    </context>
            
	<context id="addOperation">
		<description><b>Add Operation</b>
Select the operations to be added to the operation.
A resource can have at most one operation for each method.
Those operations already in the resource are checked, and cannot be selected again.
		</description>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12016_.htm" label="Developing integration solutions by using REST APIs"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12040_.htm" label="Defining resources, models, and operations in a REST API"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12017_.htm" label="REST APIs"/>
    </context>
            
	<context id="confirmSchemaTypeChange">
		<description><b>Confirm Schema Type Change</b>
You are about to change the schema type of an operation request or response body.
The current schema type is defined inline with the body, which is not supported by the REST API editor.
With the REST API editor, you must define a model, and make the request or response body to reference the model.
If you change the inlined schema type to another type, you will not be able to change the type back using the REST API editor.
		</description>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12017_.htm" label="REST APIs"/>
    </context>
            
	<context id="confirmForSubflow">
		<description><b>Confirm Save REST API</b>
Confirm to save REST API changes before an operation related to an implementation subflow.
The REST API editor needs to be saved in order for a subflow to reference the current content of the REST API.
The saving of the REST API is performed before the following actions:
 <ul>
  <li>Create an implementing subflow for an operation</li>
  <li>Open the implementation subflow for an operation</li>
  <li>Create an implementing subflow for an error handler</li>
  <li>Open the implementation subflow for an error handler</li>
  <li>Rename an operation</li>
</ul> 
        </description>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12016_.htm" label="Developing integration solutions by using REST APIs"/>
 		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12017_.htm" label="REST APIs"/>
    </context>
            
    <context id="wizardCreate">
		<description><b>REST API Wizard</b>
Use this wizard to create a REST API Project. REST API projects implement a RESTful interface.  
Enter a name for the REST API project.
When creating a REST API from scratch, the REST API project name will also be the name of the REST API.
When importing a Swagger document, the name of the REST API is in the Swagger.
The REST API name, base path and version can be edited after the REST API is created.
		</description>
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12019_.htm" label="Creating a REST API that is based on a Swagger file"/>    
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12036_.htm" label="Creating a REST API from scratch by using the IBM Integration Toolkit"/> 
    </context>
            
    <context id="wizardImport">
		<description><b>REST API Wizard</b>
Import a Swagger document to create a REST API Project. REST API projects implement a RESTful interface.
You may click the hyperlink at the bottom to open a Swagger editor outside of the IIB Toolkit.
The URL location of the external Swagger editor can be edited in the Preference.
		</description>
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12019_.htm" label="Creating a REST API that is based on a Swagger file"/>  
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12035_.htm" label="Creating a REST API from an imported Swagger document"/>    
    </context>
            
    <context id="wizardReview">
		<description><b>REST API Wizard</b>
Review the content of the Swagger document to be imported.  
The content of the Swagger document can be edited after the REST API project is created.
Press the Back button if you want to import a different Swagger.
		</description>
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12019_.htm" label="Creating a REST API that is based on a Swagger file"/>    
		<topic href="../com.ibm.etools.mft.doc/bi12035_.htm" label="Creating a REST API from an imported Swagger document"/>    
    </context>
            
 </contexts>